(Howard:)How about
we split
(Sheldon:)the difference
and discuss why Austria
(Sheldon:)was an archduchy
and not just a regular duchy.
(Penny:)Okay, look, here's the thing.
I like pharmaceutical sales--
(Penny:)it's going great-- but I have
an audition for a movie,
(Penny:)and if I get it,
it could screw everything up.
(Sheldon:)Hmm. I know
exactly what you should do.
(Sheldon:)Unfortunately,
I cannot tell you.
(Penny:)Well, why?
(sighs)
(Sheldon:)I'm attempting
to turn over a new leaf.
(Sheldon:)Earlier today,
it was pointed out to me
(Sheldon:)that I tend to force my ideas
on people.
(Penny:)You're really
not gonna tell me?
(Sheldon:)No, that train has left
the station.
(Sheldon:)Now, we can
play this
(Sheldon:)one of two ways.
(Sheldon:)You can say,
"Trains, tell me more,"
(Sheldon:)or...
(Sheldon:)you can just look at me
like that
(Sheldon:)and I'll start.
(Bernadette:)What's going on
in here?
(Howard:)I am making molecular cocktails.
(Howard:)This sphere is actually
a cosmopolitan.